Jai Hind friends, welcome to this informative video.
Friends, in this video we are
discussing a very important topic.
It is related to health policy
because health policy is very important.
Today you cannot buy any plan or have
not made any investment,
but you must buy a health policy
because health policy is very
important today. If you
fall ill tomorrow, all your savings are lost. So, whether
you do anything else or not, the first thing you should do is
buy a health policy. I
definitely recommend this in all my videos
that today you should buy a
health policy from anywhere. You must buy a health policy
because it has a small premium and your
family is secure. So friends,
in this video we are talking about the
Health Cell 360 plan which used to be available in ICC Bank, which has
now been discontinued. I had
made a lot of videos for myself on Health Cell 360,
but now I get comments that that
plan is not exiting now, so yes,
that plan has been discontinued as of today.  In
place of that, now another plan has come, so in this video
we will tell you about the new plan by going through the complete one to one process.
If you have an account in ICICI Bank, then you
can check yourself
how much your premium is and
what benefits you will get in it now. So
first of all friends, if you are new to our channel then do
like and subscribe because I keep
bringing all the updates of banking and finance on this channel.
You get
to see all the notifications related to RBI Bank on my channel. So friends, let's
start the video. Friends, if you
look at ICC Lord, it is the best company
today.
If you look at your health policy, its market share is very
good. You can go to any hospital and
get cashless benefits.
You get many facilities in it and the claim
settlement is very good. Along with this, see
application based, you can raise a claim in it
and you also get 247 customer care service.
So let me take you and
we will talk regarding the new policy that has come. First of all, you should
look at it one to one carefully and understand.
Go and you will not need any consultant or
any banker, you
can see the details of this policy yourself and if it is
better for you then you should definitely purchase it,
definitely recommend it to your friends and family,
I will put its link
in my description box, from there
you can check the link and if you have an
account in ICC Bank then you will easily be able to access it, so
first of all friends
if you see the Health 360 plan,
only in it you will see the renewal option,
only you can renew the Health Cell 360, the one
you have already taken, there is
no process to buy it because the policy has now been closed,
now the new policy as of today
is Elevate Policy, there are three types of plans in it,
you can see the plan which will be best for you, so I will
tell you the one to one process one by one, like if you
click on Buy Now then it is
necessary for you to have an account in ICC Bank, for this
you will see that the entire process will be one to one
in it and all the benefits are available
here  You will get to see it, so do
not skip the video, see one by one what all you have to
see, how
is the process and what you have to see, see everything, ICB
customer details are being asked here, so
first of all your name is there, so
enter your name here, you have to enter the same mobile number which is
registered in your account,
after that you have to enter the PAN number,
as you enter all the three details inside it,
you have to click on the submit box, if you
click on the submit box, then all
your date of birth and details in the ICB bank accounts are
automatically fetched, after this you have to
submit the OTP, the OTP will
come on your registered mobile,
as soon as you submit the OTP,
you will see your successful pop up, as soon as
you submit, a new
window will open in which
you will see everything regarding your address,
first of all this page is a very
important page, in this you have to see which is
suffering from pre [music] agistify and then
you face problem in getting its claim,
but before that if you
Tell the company that this is an issue with us, then
you will already have it
declared with the bank, and you will easily get its
claim, so you will see, first of all
you should read everything one by one, if not then
no pre-registration,
so you can select whichever you want,
suppose if I
want a plan of 1 crore then click on 1 crore,
then the complete details
will open for you, you will see in it what is the tenor, you
can take the plan for 1 year, 2 years, 3 years, once you
pay the premium for 3 years, you will be tension free for 3 years, if there is
any problem at any time, your
family will be secure, after that you will see,
your complete details will come in it, here
if you want to add someone in your family then you
can go to add adult and add, if you want to add a child then you
can go to add child and add, as you will
calculate the premium and click, then you will see
here you will see the
premium, as you do, see here the annual
income  It is necessary to declare
annual income as on today's date. As soon as you declare it,
click on calculate here. If you click on calculate, then the
complete details will open as to
how many types of plans are there and which one will be
best for you. So, see in this, there are
three types of plans, basic, essential and
recommended. In this, see, there are three types
of premiums for all three, ₹ 3462, ₹
469, ₹
3281. This is inclusive of GST. So, if
you see everything here,
you can view here one by one the benefit of which you want to see
or
you can read its benefits by going to view benefits. And one more thing, the
pre-post claim process in the bank has
changed now. It has now become 90 days and
180 days. Suppose if
you have taken a claim for someone and he
is suffering from illness for 60 days, then whatever
your expenses are,
you will get the entire expense of that. What is there after
180 days?  Whatever your treatment will be for up to 90 months, the
doctor will prescribe you this medicine, you have to
take it for 3 months or you have to get a checkup done, then
you will be covered for up to 3 months also, so if you
look at everything, there are many
benefits, first of all if you
go to the benefits in this recruitment, then you get unlimited
cover in it and there is unlimited time
reset facility in it and many more
benefits, see the covers in it,
your PD cover starts after 90 days, there is
wellness program, in this
you get health checkup facility,
see in this you also get loyalty bonus,
if you are not taking a claim then you will get a
loyalty bonus of 20% from your next
premium, there is reset benefit,
you get reset benefit for unlimited times,
what was the earlier that if
you took a claim for any disease, then you
could not take a claim for the second time for the same disease, but now
you can take claim unlimited times, in this all the
surgeries, domestic surgeries are covered up
to  You can avail sums, it has up to some sod,
apart from this, see home care treatment
is not applicable in it, after that if you
look at the
cover that is included in it, it is the best, I will tell you,
Ayush treatment is also included in it, there is
no capping on room rent,
you can take even a single private room under it, so
you get all these benefits
now, apart from this, if you look at so many
additional covers, if you look at the additional cover in it, you get the
facility of claim product annual health checkup,
you can also get a health checkup done for the entire family for the same amount as the premium,
so if you go for a health checkup today, then there is a
health checkup worth Rs. 45000, which will be
free of cost for you in this policy, so you get
power booster
facility in it, daily consultancy is
also there, if you fall ill tomorrow, then
you do not need to go to the OPD,
you can also take tele consultation online on your own,
so friends, there are many benefits in this policy  There are benefits in it, if you have
your ICE bank account then by
clicking on the link you can see and
understand everything, this is a very best policy
and I would recommend you to
go for the policy which is recommendatory in it, it is essential and basic also, there are
all the benefits in it, you should
see it yourself and understand it yourself, then definitely write about its policy
in the comments that how did you like the policy, so
friends I hope the video is
very informative, please like and share it,
thank you very much